CO_ID	YYYY/MM	Quarter	consolidation	Month	Currency	Gross operating revenue	Total rental revenue	Operating revenue - Disposal of lands	Interest revenue	Operating revenue - disposal of investments	Total investment revenue	Sales discounts and allowances	Total operating revenue	Cost of goods sold (A) 　	Operating cost - Rent	Operating cost - disposal of lands	Interest expense	Operating cost - disposal of investments	Total investment losses	Total operating costs	Gross profit (loss) from operations	Realized (unrealized) profit - affliated companies	Realized gross operating profit	Total operating expenses	Total selling expenses	Total administrative expenses	Total research and development expenses	"Other expense, by function"	Expected credit impairment (loss) gain	Net other income (expenses)	Net operating income (loss)	Total interest income	Rent income	Revenue from royalties	Revenue from dividends	Gain recognised in bargain purchase transaction	Income from counter-party default	Gains on expected credit impairment	Gains on write-off of past due payable	Government grants income	"Other income, others"	Other Non-Operating Income	"Gains on disposals of property, plant and equipment"	Gains on disposals of investments	Foreign exchange gains	Gains on financial assets (liabilities) at fair value through profit or loss	Gain on financial liabilities measured at amortized cost	Gain on hedging instrument	Gain on valuation of assets	"Reversal of impairment loss recognised in profit or loss, financial assets"	Reversal of loss on assets impairment	Reversal of loss on PP&E	Reversal of loss on intangible assets	Other reversal of loss	Compensation income	Gains on corporate bonds repurchases	Losses on work stoppages	Guarantee contracts losses	Compensation losses	"Losses on disposals of property, plant and equipment"	Losses on disposals of investments	Foreign exchange losses	Losses on financial assets (liabilities) at fair value through profit or loss	Loss on financial liabilities measured at amortized cost	Loss on hedging instrument	Loss on contract	Impairment loss on financial assets	"Impairment loss recognised in profit or loss, property, plant and equipment"	PP&E impairment loss	Intangible assets impairment loss	Other impairment loss	Losses on corporate bonds repurchases	"Other gains and losses, other"	"Other gains and losses, net"	Total interest expense(excluding lease liabilities)	Interest expense on lease liabilities	Dividends on preference share liabilities	"Finance costs, other"	"Finance costs, net"	Share of profit of associates and joint ventures accounted for using equity meth	Share of loss of associates and joint ventures accounted for using equity method	Share of profit(loss) of associates &joint ventures accounted for using eq. meth	Gain (loss) on expected credit impairment	Gain (loss) on derecognition of fin. assets meas. at amortized cost	Gain (loss) on financial assets reclassification	"Non-operating income and expenses, other"	Total non-operating income and expenses	Profit (loss) before tax	Total tax expense (income)	Profit (loss) from continuing operations	Total profit (loss) from discontinued operations	"Comprehensive income, attributable to non-controlling interests in pre-aquisitio"	Other adj. item - I/S	Profit (loss)	OCI-Remeasurement of defined benefit plans - not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Gain (loss) on revaluation of property - not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Credit risk on FV measurement of FL - not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Non-curr. assets held for sale or assigned owners-not reclassified to P/L	OCI-Unrealized G(L) on FVOCI investments in equity - not reclassified to P/L	OCI-Gain(loss) on hedging instrucment - not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Gain(loss) on share of associate&joint venture acc.-not reclassified to P/L	OCI-Others - not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Income tax relating to components - not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Items that are not reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Translat. diff. of foreign operat. agency's report-maybe reclassified to P/L	OCI-Non-curr. assets held for sale or assigned owners-maybe reclassified to P/L	OCI-Unrealized G(L) on FVOCI investment in debt instr.-maybe reclassified to P/L	OCI-Gain(loss) on hedging instrucment - maybe reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-G(L) on share of associate&joint venture acc.-maybe reclassified to P/L	OCI-Others - maybe reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Income tax relating to components - maybe reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Subsequent items that are or maybe reclassified to profit or loss	OCI-Attributable to non-controlling interest in pre-acquisition share capital	"Other comprehensive income, net"	Comprehensive income	"Profit (loss), attributable to owners of parent"	"Profit (loss), attributable to non-controlling interests"	"Profit (loss), attributable to interests in the former jointly controlled entity"	"Comprehensive income, attributable to owners of parent"	"Comprehensive income, attributable to non-controlling interests"	"Comprehensive income, attributable to non-controlling interest in pre-aquisition"	Total basic earnings per share	Average common shares (Thousand)	Preferred stock dividends	Diluted net income	Total diluted earnings per share	Average diluted common shares (Thousand)	Earnings before interest and tax	"Earnings before interest, tax, depreciation and amortization"	Recurring net income	Treasury shares-buys back	Treasury shares-subsidiary holding	Total treasury shares
1216 Uni-President	2023/12	4	Y	12	NTD	581102935.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	581102935.00 	393289237.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	393289237.00 	187813698.00 	0.00 	187813698.00 	159172864.00 	132254342.00 	25823949.00 	1021795.00 	0.00 	72778.00 	0.00 	28640834.00 	4744321.00 	908028.00 	0.00 	225770.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	713531.00 	3264905.00 	9856555.00 	0.00 	10914814.00 	120087.00 	443356.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	311.00 	311.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	69025.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	(293308.00)	11116235.00 	2037938.00 	1470609.00 	0.00 	(17755.00)	3490792.00 	2568114.00 	-	2568114.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	20050112.00 	48690946.00 	18404797.00 	30286149.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	30286149.00 	305672.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	273100.00 	0.00 	(61100.00)	0.00 	68280.00 	449392.00 	(2694437.00)	0.00 	21025.00 	0.00 	145506.00 	0.00 	(326.00)	(2527580.00)	0.00 	(2078188.00)	28207961.00 	18336478.00 	11949671.00 	0.00 	17032800.00 	11175161.00 	0.00 	3.23 	5682015.00 	0.00 	18336478.00 	3.21 	5708710.00 	52181738.00 	90972681.00 	18996693.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 
1217 AGV	2023/12	4	Y	12	NTD	5273175.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	373137.00 	4900038.00 	3486325.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	3486325.00 	1413713.00 	0.00 	1413713.00 	1284939.00 	917363.00 	317411.00 	48171.00 	0.00 	1994.00 	0.00 	128774.00 	4470.00 	11623.00 	0.00 	16778.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	29833.00 	62704.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	5736.00 	0.00 	0.00 	52193.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	164.00 	0.00 	3664.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	18552.00 	18552.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	(21097.00)	14452.00 	124642.00 	1105.00 	0.00 	7019.00 	132766.00 	187988.00 	-	187988.00 	(410.00)	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	131968.00 	260742.00 	43142.00 	217600.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 	217600.00 	(4787.00)	87587.00 	0.00 	0.00 	(131897.00)	0.00 	93912.00 	0.00 	(29.00)	44844.00 	(5572.00)	0.00 	2900.00 	0.00 	(4908.00)	0.00 	(840.00)	(6740.00)	0.00 	38104.00 	255704.00 	200936.00 	16664.00 	0.00 	246897.00 	8807.00 	0.00 	0.41 	494513.00 	0.00 	200936.00 	0.41 	494829.00 	393508.00 	524469.00 	178387.00 	0.00 	0.00 	0.00 
